ahalogy.com 2014-06-21

# Ahalogy | Privacy Policy

Please read this privacy policy carefully before visiting or using the website.

#### Ahalogy's Thoughts on Privacy

MLW Squared, Inc. (“Ahalogy”), has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate its commitment to privacy. We urge you to read the entire privacy policy so you will understand all of the practices and procedures we follow relating to your on- line privacy.

#### What This Privacy Policy Covers

The Website is the responsibility of Ahalogy. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the Website, or your visit to or use of the Website, you can contact us by e-mail at info@Ahalogynow.com, or by U.S. Mail at Ahalogy, 3197 Linwood Avenue, Cincinnati, OH 45208. You can reach us by phone at 513-620-8595.

#### What Kind of Personal Information Ahalogy Collects

The privacy and security of your information is important to us. We give you the option of signing up to receive email updates. If you choose to register with us, we require you to give us your name and e-mail address. In addition, the Website collects contact information in connection with other visitors or users whom you will interact with the Website. We take care to protect the online data you submit to us when using the Website and store such information in a secure database.

Additionally, some information about your server address, web browser, and computer system are automatically transmitted to our web servers so that we can operate and improve the Website. For example, we track the number of people who view each page, the order in which pages are viewed, and other information to learn which features are the most popular and to refine our design and marketing efforts. We collect and store such information on an aggregated (collected) basis.

As part of the Website operation, we reserve the right to collect automatically and track:

The home server, IP addresses and domain names, e-mail addresses, type of computer, and type of web browser you are using while you visit the Website; and

Other information volunteered by you when you use the Website.

#### How We Use Your Personal Information

Email Sign-Up: When you provide us with your email address we may use that information to contact you by email to maintain and update your Every Day account, to send you updates about new services and noteworthy news and events, to get in touch with you in response to forms such as “Contact US” or e-mailed support requests or about a material change to this Privacy Policy or the Terms and Conditions, or to comply with applicable statutes and regulations or legal process served on Ahalogy.

Aggregated Uses of Information:

• IP addresses are used to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Website. In addition, your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

• Demographic and profile data are used only for personalized content and statistical information and are not shared with other companies except in ways that do not personally identify our users. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at the Website, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying the content according to your preferences.

In all cases, users may opt out of receiving future mailings. Please see the “Opting-Out” section below for more information.

**Ahalogy will not share your e-mail address with anyone else**.

#### Public Message Boards and Forums

The Website may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### Security

The security of all personally identifying information associated with our users is of great concern to us. Although "perfect security" does not exist in any transaction process on line or in physical stores, the Website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please be assured that we are constantly reviewing our security processes to keep up to date with the absolute highest levels of security encryption and service.

#### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small file sent from a web server to your browser and is stored on your computer’s hard drive when you visit certain Websites. Cookies help web surfing by saving visitor preferences and other information. The use of cookies is a widespread industry standard and thus many major Websites use cookies.

Most Web browsers are initially configured to accept and process cookies. You can configure your browser to refuse cookies.

Ahalogy uses cookies to keep track of your logged-in status. We reserve the right to use cookies to customize content based on the pages you have looked at. If you have any questions concerning our use of cookies, please contact us at info@Ahalogynow.com.

#### Opting-Out

The Website provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. At your request, we shall remove all of your information from our database.

You can send your request by e-mail to info@Ahalogynow.com, or by phone or U.S. Mail, in order to unsubscribe from any or all email lists.

#### Requesting to See Your Personal Information

You may request via e-mail, U.S. Mail or telephone that we provide you with the personal information we have concerning you. Once you receive this information, you may request that we modify or remove any of your personal information. We reserve the right to verify your identity before sending you this information.

#### Links to Other Websites

The Website contains links to other Websites or websites. Ahalogy is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites or websites. Occasionally, you may receive cookies from third-party advertisers, partners and vendors. We do not control these cookies.

#### Access to Children

There are no features of the Website directed to children under the age of 13. Children under 13 may not register with Ahalogy, or use any of the services available on the Website.

Although the Website and sites that Ahalogy powers are not currently directed to children under the age of 13, any forthcoming sites that interact with children under 13 will always obtain parental consent prior to collecting personal information. Such sites will also provide parents with access to information collected about their child and the opportunity to opt out of future collection and have us delete such information. Without prior parental consent, Ahalogy will use a child’s online information only to respond directly to the child's request and will not use it for other purposes without prior parental consent.

Ahalogy strongly encourages parents and guardians to supervise their children's online activities and to consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools also can prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personally identifiable information without parental permission. Products and services for sale are intended for purchase by adults. By making a purchase on the Website, you agree that you are at least 13 years of age.

Ahalogy and the Websites and other websites that Ahalogy powers will...

NOT collect personally identifiable off-line contact information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.

NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with respect to children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.

NOT give the ability to post publicly or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information with respect to children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.

NOT entice children under the age of 13 by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. We ask that you review this privacy policy from time to time to ensure you are familiar with the most current version of it.

#### Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By visiting or using the Website, you agree to the terms as well as any posted changes of this Privacy Policy. By visiting or using the Website, you hereby consent to the collection and use of this information by Ahalogy. If you do not agree to the terms, DO NOT use the Website.

_Date of last update: Oct 10, 2013_
